Rohit Kumar Singh

India



rohitkrsingh08@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/rohit-singh-08

Summary

I have working experience in power plant industry for two year. In addition to that I know basic designing and coding. I occasionally indulge in side hobbies like building small electronics projects and bots.

Also, I am an avid gamer and a numismatist.

Experience



Manager

Reliance Industries Limited

Aug 2017 - Dec 2019 (2 years 5 months)

Internship

Garden Reach Shipbuilders & Engineers

Jun 2016 - Jul 2016 (2 months)

The intership involved maintenance and service of diesel engine used for marine application.

Intership

Heavy Engineering corporation

Jun 2015 - Jul 2015 (2 months)

My work at HEC Ltd, involved looking after production process. The production process involved manufacturing of steel products (casting and forged), their machining and finishing.

Education



Manipal Institute of Technology

Bachelor of Technology (BTech), Mechanical Engineering 2013 - 2017

🔰 Jawahar Vidya Mandir Shyamali

CBSE 12th, Science 2012 - 2013



St. Thomas School

ICSE 10th 2010 - 2011

Skills

Microsoft Office • Customer Service • Microsoft Excel • Management • Microsoft Word • Microsoft PowerPoint • Public Speaking • Research Skills • Project Management • Leadership